Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 55, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Development of Our Manpower Resources, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Wasted Manpower, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Author: War Advertising Council
  - Item 7: Worker Mobility and Skill Utilization in World War II, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Incentive Contracts and Technical Manpower, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Author: Deutsch & Shea, Inc.
  - Item 9: The Emerging Labor Force, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Box: 55, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Basic Level Manpower Utilization and Talent Development and the Social Sciences, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Author: John McCollum
  - Item 2: Manpower Requirements for National Objectives in the 1970's, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Pilot University Research Consultation Conference, 1967; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Author: Pennsylvania State University
  - Item 4: Improved Manpower Management in the Federal Government, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Author: U.S. Subcommittee on Manpower
  - Item 5: Study of Manpower Utilization in Financial Management Functions in the Defense Establishment, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Notes: June 1964
  - Item 6: Manpower Projections, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The Emerging Labor Force, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Box: 55, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How Research Can Help Training, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Author: Hilary M. Clay
- Box: 55, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Map of Ontario, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Author: Gulf
- Box: 55, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Applicability of United States Laws to Foreign Seamen on Foreign Flag Vessels, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph Alton Jenkins
    Notes: January 30, 1961
- Box: 55, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: American Industry Looks Ahead, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Box: 55, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Modern Marketing Management, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Author: Shoji Murata
- Box: 55, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Marxism in the United States, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Box: 55, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Community Economic Inventory, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Author: Maryland Department of Economic Development
  - Item 2: Business Births and Deaths, 1948; Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Notes: May 1948
- Box: 55, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Sources of Social and Economic Statistics for Massachusetts, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Box: 55, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Immigrant Population of Massachusetts, 1913; Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Author: Massachusetts Bureau of Statistics
    Notes: April 30, 1913
- Box: 55, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Industrial Pattern of Massachusetts, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Box: 55, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Political Activities of Public Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
    Notes: December 21, 1964
- Box: 55, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Maternity Protection for Women Workers in Canada, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Box: 55, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employment in Professional Mathematical Work in Industry and Government, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Box: 55, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Mathematics in Industrial Relations, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Author: Thomas A. Mahoney
- Box: 55, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Civilian Meat Distribution, 1944; Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Office of Price Administration
    Notes: January - March 1944
- Box: 55, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Meat Packing, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Box: 55, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Injuries and Accident Causes in the Slaughtering and Meat-Packing Industry, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Box: 55, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Progress Report Automation Committee, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
    Author: Armour and Automation Committee
- Box: 55, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Postwar Labor Policy, 1945; Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The Use of Informed Neutrals in Difficult Bargaining Situations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: State Authorities Engaged in Mediation and Conciliation Activities, 1947; Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Box: 55, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Mediation and Arbitration of Labor Disputes, 1942; Publication (Box 55, Folder 22)
    Author: Harold Bruss Baker
- Box: 55, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Troikas, Duets and Prima Donnas in Labor Mediation, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
    Author: Robert L. Stutz
- Box: 55, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Manual for Mediation and Emergency Boards, 1945; Publication (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Box: 55, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Federal Mediator Positions, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
    Author: Federal Mediation & Conciliation Service
  - Item 2: Labor Adjustment Machinery, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
    Author: Herbert R. Northrup
- Box: 55, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Mediation and Mediators: A Summary of Published Materials, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
    Author: U.S. Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service
- Box: 55, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Brief Summary of State Mediation Laws, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Box: 55, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Health Manpower Act of 1968, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
    Notes: June 21, 1968
  - Item 2: Health Manpower Act of 1968, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 3, 1968
  - Item 3: The Consumer's Stake in Medical Care, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
    Author: Sidney Hillman Foundation
  - Item 4: Health Services Amendments, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 12, 1968
- Box: 55, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Sixth Institute on Rehabilitation Services, Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
    Author: U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare
  - Item 2: Allied Health Professions Personnel Training Act of 1966, Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
    Notes: October 13, 1966
  - Item 3: Health Service Amendments of 1968, Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
    Notes: July 24, 1968
  - Item 4: Health Manpower Source Book, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Nursing Homes and Related Health Care Facilities, 1969; Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: What Is Management's Responsibility for the Medical Care of its Employees?, 1946; Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
    Notes: April 14, 1946
- Box: 55, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: United States Statistics on Medical Economics, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Meeting Medical Care Costs Among the Aging, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
    Author: Ethel Shanas
  - Item 3: Family Expenditure Patterns for Personal Health Services, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
    Author: Health Information Foundation
  - Item 4: Farmers' Expenditures for Health Care in 1955, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. Department of Agriculture
  - Item 5: Medical Care, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Economic Costs of Cardiovascular Diseases and Cancer, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: The Layman's View About the Costs of Medical Care, 1935; Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
    Author: Julius Rosenwald Fund
    Notes: March 1935
- Box: 55, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Occupations in the Care and Rehabilitation of the Mentally Retarded, Publication (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Box: 55, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Extension of Programs for Training in the Allied Health Professions, 1970; Publication (Box 55, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 30, 1970
- Box: 55, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Utilization of Rehabilitation Manpower in the Community Setting, Publication (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Box: 55, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Attendants in American Mental Hospitals, Publication (Box 55, Folder 34)
    Author: Richard L. Simpson
  - Item 2: Health Manpower, 1967; Publication (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Box: 55, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Better Doctoring - Less Dependency, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: Louise Stevens Bryant
  - Item 2: Medical Care for a Million People, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: United Hospital Fund of New York
  - Item 3: What Private Medicine Costs the Average American, 1946; Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: Insurance Economics Society of America
  - Item 4: Something Can Be Done About Chronic Illness, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: Herbert Yahraes
  - Item 5: Medical Group Practice in the United States, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: U.S. Public Health Service
  - Item 6: Medical Resources Available to Meet the Needs of Public Assistance Recipients, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: Better Medical Care for More People, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: John V. Lawrence
  - Item 8: Blueprints for Medicine's Tomorrow, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Author: New York University
  - Item 9: Medical Care for the Individual and the Issue of Compulsory Health Insurance, 1948; Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
- Box: 55, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Management Health Centers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 36)
    Author: American Medical Association
  - Item 2: Comprehensive Medical Insurance, Publication (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: The Responsibility for Medical and Hospital Care -- State or Individual, 1950; Publication (Box 55, Folder 36)
    Author: Harry Becker
    Notes: March 22, 1950
- Box: 55, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Czechoslovakia Health Services, 1966; Publication (Box 55, Folder 37)
    Author: Orbis
- Box: 55, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: New Plans of Medical Service, 1936; Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: To Improve Medical Care, Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Family Hospital and Surgical Insurance Coverage, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
    Notes: July 1962 - June 1963
  - Item 4: Public Assistance, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
    Notes: June 30, 1968
  - Item 5: Health: Are We the People Getting Our Money's Worth?, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
    Author: Helen Mill Miller
    Notes: November 9, 1963
- Box: 55, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Information for Home Attendants, Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
    Author: New York Employment Service
  - Item 2: Family Health Expenses, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
    Notes: July-December 1962
  - Item 3: Personal Health Expenses, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: Medical Care, Health Status, and Family Income, Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: Economic Aspects of Prolonged Illness, 1951; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
    Author: Research Council for Economic Security
  - Item 6: Medical Costs and Control, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
    Author: A.W. Randall
    Notes: October 4, 1961
  - Item 7: The Impact of Hospitalization Costs, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Item 8: Medical Assistance Financed Under the Public Assistance Titles, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Item 9: Medical Care, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
- Box: 56, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Public Assistance Medical Care, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Author: S.J. Axelrod
- Box: 56, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Gains Toward Meeting Health Care Costs, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Author: Health Insurance Association in America
  - Item 2: Medical Care Prices, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Box: 56, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Restrictions on the Supply of Medical Services in Hawaii, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Author: Frank H. Jackson
    Notes: February 1961
- Box: 56, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Medical Policies and Executive Health, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Industrial Health Programs, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: The Bureau of National Affairs, Inc.
  - Item 3: Medical Services for Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 1956
  - Item 4: A General Guide for and Occupational Health Program for Hospital Employees, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Wisconsin State Board of Health
  - Item 5: Guide to the Development of Company Medical Policies, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Functions of an Occupational Health Service in an Industrial Organisation, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Association of Industrial Medical Officers
  - Item 7: Trends in Employee Health Services, 1965; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Pension and Profit-Sharing Plans, 1963; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Chemical Bank New York Trust Company
    Notes: Spring 1963
  - Item 9: Doctors and Nurses in Industry, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Rhoda L. Goldstein, Bernard Goldstein
  - Item 10: Man, Medicine, and Work, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: First Aid Services for Factories, 1945; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labour and National Service
  - Item 12: Industrial Dental Service, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Industrial Health Examinations in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1945; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Who's Too Small for a Health Program?, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: First-Aid Service in Small Industrial Plants, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Welfare Among Dock Workers, 1951; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: National Dock Labour Board
    Notes: July 1947 - December 1951
- Box: 56, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Occupational Health Activities in Finland in 1964, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Author: The Occupational Medical Foundation
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1965; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Box: 56, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Health at Work, Publication (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Appointed Factory Doctor Service, Publication (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Box: 56, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Occupational Medicine in Spain, 1964; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Author: Pablo-Antonio Lapuente Benavente
- Box: 56, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Medical Care for Low Income Persons in New Jersey, 1968; Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Author: General Assembly of the State of New Jersey
    Notes: September 10, 1968
- Box: 56, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Health Services in Britain, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 1961
- Box: 56, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Free Choice of Physician in Hawaii's Medical Care Program, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 10)
    Author: Hawaii Legislative Reference Bureau
- Box: 56, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Health Care Crisis: Where Do We Go From Here?, 1968; Publication (Box 56, Folder 11)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther
    Notes: November 14, 1968
- Box: 56, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Age, Status and the Diffusion of Preventive Health Practices, Publication (Box 56, Folder 12)
    Author: Bert L. Ellenbogen, George D. Lowe, Robert A. Danley
- Box: 56, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Health Manpower Needs in the District of Columbia, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 13)
    Author: U.S. Committee on the District of Columbia
    Notes: June 29, 1970
- Box: 56, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: In Memphis: More than a Garbage Strike, 1968; Publication (Box 56, Folder 14)
    Author: J. Edwin Stanfield
    Notes: April 28, 1968
- Box: 56, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Mental Health Benefits of the Social Security Amdendments of 1965, Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Social Change and Mental Health, Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Author: The Park College Press
  - Item 3: Psychiatry and its Role in Industry, Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Author: John Donnelly
  - Item 4: In Pursuit of Happiness, 1963; Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Author: Norman M. Bradburn
  - Item 5: Extending Mental Health Services to Blue-Collar Workers and Low-Income Groups in San Francisco, 1965; Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Author: John Simons
    Notes: July 1965
  - Item 6: The Nervous Temperament, 1930; Publication (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Author: Millais Culpin, May Smith
- Box: 56, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Psychological Tests and Fair Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Author: Jay T. Rusmore
  - Item 2: How to Use the Wonderlic Personnel Test, Publication (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Author: E.F. Wonderlic
  - Item 3: Psychological Monographs, 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Author: American Psychological Association
  - Item 4: Using the Intelligence Test, 1958; Publication (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Author: Paul A. Schwarz
- Box: 56, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Modern Teaching Methods and the Merchant Navy, Publication (Box 56, Folder 17)
    Author: Alfred Carver
- Box: 56, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Merchant Marine Statistics, 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Treasury Department
    Notes: January 1, 1960
  - Item 2: Merchant Marine Statistics, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 1, 1961
- Box: 56, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Jobs in the U.S. Merchant Marine, Publication (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Box: 56, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: International Labor Organization Convention, 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 20)
    Notes: August 31, 1960
- Box: 56, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Seamen's Welfare in Ports, 1945; Publication (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Box: 56, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Innstilling om Revisjon av lov om Pensjonstrygd for Sjomenn, 1968; Publication (Box 56, Folder 22)
    Author: Trykt I Engers Boktrykkeri
- Box: 56, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Annual and Sick Leave for Maritime Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 23)
    Notes: March 1, 1966
  - Item 2: Leave System for Federal Seafaring Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Box: 56, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Status and Working Conditions of Seamen in the American Merchant Marine, Publication (Box 56, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Department of Commerce
- Box: 56, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Fabricated Metal Products: I, Publication (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Fabricated Metal Products: II, Publication (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Box: 56, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Metal Occupations, Publication (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Box: 56, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Metal, Machinery, Transportation Equipment, and Allied Products Industry in Puerto Rico, 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Box: 56, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Primary Metals: I, Publication (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Primary Metals: II, Publication (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Box: 56, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Safety and Health in Soldering and Brazing, Publication (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Box: 56, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Union des Metallugistes Parisiens, 1965; Publication (Box 56, Folder 30)
    Author: Georges Marchais
    Notes: October 28, 1965
- Box: 56, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Labor Conditions in Bolts, Nuts, Nails, Springs and Chains Factories in India, Publication (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Box: 56, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Report of the Interregional Symposium on Metalworking Industries in Developing Countries, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 32)
- Box: 56, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Social Creed of the Methodist Church, Publication (Box 56, Folder 33)
    Author: Board of Social and Economic Relations
- Box: 56, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Standard Metropolitan Statistical Areas, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 34)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of the Budget
- Box: 56, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The California Migrant Farm Work, His Family, and the Rural Community, Publication (Box 56, Folder 35)
    Author: University of California
  - Item 2: Segregation, Subsidies, and Megalopolis, Publication (Box 56, Folder 35)
- Box: 56, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Image, Publication (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Mexican-Americans: Problems and Prospects, Publication (Box 56, Folder 36)
    Author: Joan W. Moore
  - Item 3: The Mexican American: A National Concern, 1949; Publication (Box 56, Folder 36)
    Author: Common Council for American Unity
    Notes: Summer 1949
- Box: 56, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Labor Importation Program Between Mexico and the United States, 1948; Publication (Box 56, Folder 37)
    Author: Robert C. Jones
  - Item 2: Mexican-Americans, Publication (Box 56, Folder 37)
- Box: 56, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Mining and Manufacturing Industries in Mexico, 1946; Publication (Box 56, Folder 38)
    Author: United States Tariff Commission
- Box: 56, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: What's Ahead for Michigan?, Publication (Box 56, Folder 39)
    Author: William Haber, Eugene C. McKean, Harold C. Taylor
  - Item 2: Econometric Model of Michigan, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 39)
    Author: Michigan Department of Commerce
    Notes: April 1966
- Box: 56, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: A Report on the Characteristics of Michigan's Non-White Population, Publication (Box 56, Folder 40)
- Box: 56, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Community Organization and Development in Selected Arab Countries of the Middle East, 1953; Publication (Box 56, Folder 41)
    Notes: November 1953
- Box: 56, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Economic Fact Book, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 42)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago
- Box: 56, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Adjustment of Rural Workers to Non-Agricultural Employment and Urban Areas, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 43)
    Author: Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development
    Notes: January 5, 1967